Enter a world where magic can't save you.
DC Showcase - Constantine: The House of Mystery is a animation,
action, adventure film directed by Matt Peters.
John Constantine wakes up in the eerie House of Mystery
with no recollection of how he got there.
Fortunately, Zatanna and his friends are all there.
Unfortunately, they have a bad habit of turning into demons
and ripping him to shreds, over and over again!
Constantine (voice), played by Matt Ryan.
Jason Blood / Etrigan / Ritchie (voice), played by Ray Chase.
Gary Lester / Negral (voice), played by Robin Atkin Downes.
Beelzebub / Little Della / Little Jack (voice), played by Grey DeLisle.
Zatanna (voice), played by Camilla Luddington.
Ashox / Chas (voice), played by Damian O'Hare.
The DC Animated Movie Universe (DCAMU) is  an American media franchise and shared
universe of animated films distributed between 2013 and 2024 by Warner Bros.
Animation and DC Entertainment.
Based on characters from the DC Universe (DC Comics), the franchise is
part of the DC Universe Animated Original Movies line.
The main film series are split into two story arcs with different continuities.
The first story arc began in 2013 with Justice League: The Flashpoint Paradox and ended in 2020 with Justice League Dark: Apokolips War, while the second story arc, nicknamed
the "Tomorrowverse", began later that year with Superman: Man of Tomorrow and concluded in 2024 with the Justice League: Crisis on Infinite Earths trilogy.
The franchise comprises 25 films overall, with tie-in media including
5 short films, one web series and two digital comics.
The film explores themes of magic, superhero,
vertigo, supernatural, haunted house.
The tone is dark.